Oh my, what a rather leisurely guest we have
あらあら、随分とのんびりなさったお客様ですこと
Now, with my magic,
さあ、わたくしの魔術で
What kind of special trick would you like to experience?
どのような特別なマジックを体験したいのかしら？
Well then, could you perhaps warm things up with a simple trick first?
では、まずは簡単な手品で場を温めていただけますか？
Hmph… To summarize my art with just two words, 'simple'…
ふふふ…わたくしの芸術を
You truly underestimate people, don't you?
本当に人を見くびっているわね
…Hmph, very well.
……ふん、よろしいでしょう
If you so 'fervently' desire it,
あなたがそんなに「熱烈」に望むのなら
then I shall deign to show you
このわたくしがみつから
Pay close attention, to what truly 'simple' art looks like...
カルミラの目に映る本当の「簡単」な芸術とは何かを
...in Carmilla's eyes!
よくご覧あそばせ？
Whoa, h-how did you do that?!
うわ、こ、これはどうやって？！
No way… she really didn't notice
まさか…本当に気づかれないなんて
Looks like I can use this to temporarily erase my presence
これで俺の存在を一時的に消せるみたいだな
Heh, all that hard work paid off…
へへ、苦労した甲斐があったぜ……
The 'simple' appetizer is now over
「簡単」なアペリティフは
Now, my dear guest,
さて、わたくしの愛しいお客様
Are you ready for...
これから始まる…
The true feast that is about to begin...
あなたの魂の奥底を揺さぶる
One that will stir the depths of your soul?
真の饗宴をお迎えする準備はよろしくて？
I suggest you hold your breath and wait, won't you?
存分に期待して…
Oh, I can't wait!
おお、楽しみです！
Within this little theater,
この小さな劇場の中では…
I am the only rule, the only reality
わたくしこそが唯一のルール、唯一のリアル
What is 'illusion', and what is 'reality'?
何が「幻想」で、何が「現実」か
That boundary line, I shall define it for you myself
その境界線は、このわたくしが
This… from an age so long it borders on eternity…
これが…わたくしが長きに渡る永遠にも近い歳月から……
… I have painstakingly collected them
…丹精込めて蒐集いたしました
The fragments of memory… that only ephemeral beings called 'humans' possess
「人間」という儚きものだけが持つ……記憶の欠片
…Th-that scared me…!
……び、びびった…！
Shit, I thought she found me…
クソ、見つかったかと思ったぜ……
…Within these…
…この中には…
There are wails of despair, and shouts of ecstasy
絶望の慟哭も、狂喜の叫びもございますわ
There is love that leads to death, and hatred that burns the heart to cinders…
死に至るまでの愛も、心を焼き尽くす憎しみも……
The so-called 'radiance', the so-called 'shadows',
いわゆる「輝き」も、いわゆる「陰り」も
All compose this phantom we call the world
全てはこの世界という幻を構成する
…The most truthful cornerstones of 'emotion'
……最も真実なる感情の礎石
Now, my guest
さぁ、お客様
From among these myriad lights that float and fade,
あなたはこの数多の浮かんでは消える光の中から
Your own truth… what will you… be able to see… I wonder…?
ご自身の真実を…… 何をご覧に…なれ…ます…こと…
Th-this is incredible! Is this really a magic trick!?
こ……これはすごい！これは本当に手品なんですか！？
…It is merely… merely with the light and shadows…
……ただ……ただ光と影の……
… Using some trivial techniques…
……些細な技巧を使いまして
To your…
あなたの……
To your brain…
あなたの脳に……
Showing it… some… some wonderful… illusions…
いくらかの……いくらか素晴らしい……幻想を……
That is all it is…
見せて……いるだけに……ございます
It is just… just that I…
…ただわたくし…
...someone like Carmilla…
…カルミラのような
…Nnhaah!
……んああ！
…Only a great… a grand magician…
……偉大なる……大魔術師だけが……
…can perfectly… accomplish… accomplish this…
……完璧に……これを……これを成し遂げることが……
You see…
できますのよ……
… Well then…
……では……んあっ！
…The feast… of the mind…
……精神の……饗宴は……
You have… already… partaken… of it…
あなたはもう……お召し上がりに……なったので……
… Next… shall… shall we experience… a more… 'truthful'… ma… magic…?
……次は……も、もっと……真実に近い魔……魔術を
……体験……なさい……ますか……？
……体験……なさい……ますか……？
Heh heh, before that,
へへ、その前によ
How about you first get a good taste of the hot semen from my 'real' dick!
まずは俺様のこの「本物」のチンポから出る熱い精液をたっぷり味わ いな！
You like getting creampied by me, don't you, bitch? Huh?
ふうふう……このアマ、俺に中出しされて気持ちよかったか？ん？
In that case…
それでは…
KYAAAAAAAAAAH----!!!!
…きゃあああああ――！！！！
Huh? A-are you alright?
え？ だ、大丈夫でございますか？